No one comes up here without a damn good reason.
The Hateful Eight is a drama, mystery, western
film directed by Quentin Tarantino.
Bounty hunters seek shelter from a raging blizzard and get
caught up in a plot of betrayal and deception.
Major Marquis Warren, played by Samuel L. Jackson.
John 'The Hangman' Ruth, played by Kurt Russell.
Daisy Domergue, played by Jennifer Jason Leigh.
Sheriff Chris Mannix, played by Walton Goggins.
Bob, played by Demián Bichir.
Oswaldo Mobray, played by Tim Roth.
The Hateful Eight is a 2015 American Western mystery thriller
film written and directed by Quentin Tarantino.
It stars Samuel L.
Jackson, Kurt Russell, Jennifer Jason Leigh, Walton Goggins, Demián Bichir, Tim Roth, Michael Madsen, and Bruce Dern as eight
dubious strangers who seek refuge from a blizzard in a stagecoach stopover a decade after the American Civil War.
Tarantino announced the film in November 2013.
He conceived it as a novel and sequel to his 2012 film Django
Unchained before deciding to make it a standalone film.
After the script leaked in January 2014, he decided to abandon
the production and publish it as a novel instead.
In April 2014, Tarantino directed a live reading of the script at the United Artists Theater
in Los Angeles, before reconsidering a new draft and resuming the project.
Filming began in January 2015 near Telluride, Colorado.
Italian composer Ennio Morricone composed the original score, his first complete Western score in 34 years (and the last before his death
in 2020), his first for a high-profile Hollywood production since 2000, and the only original score for a Tarantino film.
Distributed by the Weinstein Company in the United States, The Hateful Eight was released on December 25, 2015,
in a limited roadshow release on 70 mm film, before expanding wide theatrically five days later.
The film was praised for its direction, screenplay, score, cinematography, and performances, though its editing,
length, the depiction of race relations and the violent treatment of Leigh's character divided opinions.
It grossed over $161 million worldwide.
For his work on the score, Morricone won his only Academy Award for
Best Original Score after five previous nominations.
The film also earned Oscar nominations for Best Supporting Actress
(Leigh) and Best Cinematography (Robert Richardson).
In 2019, a re-edited version of the film was released as a four-episode
miniseries on Netflix with the subtitle Extended Version.
The Hateful Eight was Tarantino's final collaboration with the Weinstein Company before allegations of sexual
abuse against Harvey Weinstein in 2017, which led to the former severing all ties with the latter.
The film explores themes of bounty hunter, wyoming,
usa, narration, mountain, hangman.
The tone is emotional and mind_bending.